Tani's scouting the area, so let's change it up.
Focus on the answers in front.
Might be able to rack up some kills.
My head hurts.
Hmm. The next map in particular.
Is that... yeah, someone's talking.
I told you, I'm not turning on my camera.
Who is it?
This is getting old.
Hmm?
Hey, uh...
My bad. I'm gonna go AFK.
Be right back.
Hold on.
What happened?
Hey, uh...
Yes?
Oh my gosh.
No way.
Don't tell me that we...
We didn't have a one-night stand, did we?
You really think so?
Honestly, no.
You want me right now.
That's the way I was...
That's all.
I have a pretty cool time.
Do you know what we're doing?
I don't know if we watched.
We don't know what we're doing right now.
long story short it was either take care of you or abandon you to fend for yourself on the street
but that seemed too inhumane even for me so i am deeply sorry for the trouble
i'll thank you properly no matter just leave now and we'll consider your debt paid
heading that way as we speak
by the way you're close the ones you puked on
i washed and hung them up in the bathroom oh and i also paid your bill for dinner
sorry again i'll pay you back immediately this is awful excuse me there at your bathroom
out there on the right i'll never live this down
well i doubt i'll be seeing you after today so take care
now i've gone and done it i can't believe i spent the night at the apartment of a guy i just met
hope you can forgive me all the way from gunma mom
i'm wiped
and i've still gotta work on my paper
wait
i'm not imagining it right i was wearing a necklace
but where'd it go
it's gone
your clothes the ones you puked on i washed and hung them up in the bathroom
could i have
dropped it in yamada's apartment
akanechi hey
purihime how are you
now focus where's yamada
offline
i know i had it when we were at the izakaya
i must have dropped it after we left
which can only mean it happened when i took off my clothes at yamada's place
what now
that necklace
was the first present i ever got from takuma
what's the matter did you freeze up on me akanechi
you doing okay over there
you're always the cutest breath of fresh air
oh
you poor dear
you got dumped by your boyfriend and now you've lost your precious necklace
rudy understands
since rudy gets tons of presents from her adoring fans and they're all so precious to her
each one is uniquely memorable
as fate would have it so i've been running out of space to store them all
you know
wow
oh yamada hello
yeah hello
yamada's here
now what
let's chat yamada
we were in the middle of discussing romance
get in on this
i can't it's almost time for the boss to spawn
you're going after the boss again
there's a double drop campaign
huh
what until when
they're so into it i can't get a word in edgewise
guess i'll have to pm him
oh he noticed
that was quick
why's he gotta be this way
come and talk with us yamada
it won't take long
you'd be helping me cheer up akanechi
no thanks
and besides that
what i'd like to discuss
is the storage here is always stuffed to the brim and unusable
what
hey you're right
it's bursting with items
guess i haven't been checking on it all that much
because i'm the one cleaning it out
but next thing i know it's full again
that is mighty curious
if it's not at yamada's place
is it at the izakaya after all
i wonder if someone's putting items in there out of goodwill
oh i'm the one that's
this trash out of goodwill
trash is too harsh
a guild member must have put those items in
in order to help the beginners
even a noob who just started three minutes ago
would have better gear than this junk
now now
be nice
what if it's a guild member who happens to be online
they would be crushed to see this in the chat
it was me
they're in the way
well i'm the one cleaning up that trash
don't i get a say
would you stop calling it trash
really
akanechi was only trying to be considerate
then you can start by being more selective
there's only so much storage to be had
yamada stop it
i can't what you're saying
but you could at least be a tease
you made nicer about it you bad boy
bad
aww
ow
what was that
well that's awkward
i hate you yamada
listen akane
i'm so sorry
i wasn't thinking clearly back then
but i've come to my senses
takuma
this is for you
if you'll accept
i want you to have this peace offering
i'm so happy
takuma
what a nightmare
more like a prophetic dream if you want my take
say momo you sure you're not enjoying this
no not really
especially since your takuma stores are getting old
plus that wasn't even a genuine laugh
anyway what i would enjoy is hearing all about that hot gamer nerd you met at the event
you spent the entire night with him
are you sure nothing happened
you're asking that again
for the last time no
yamada just helped me
that's all there is to it
that reminds me
what am i gonna do about the necklace takuma gave to me
i think i dropped it at yamada's place
but i can't say for sure
huh
why would you want to hold on to a gift from the guy who jilted you
you still not over him
i guess that's just the kind of person you are
you can't help always scheduling things around him
even your initial interest in online games was because of the guy
oh and didn't you make him homemade lunchboxes when you first started going out
overall you're way too doting
i get it
i won't talk about takuma anymore so please stop
as long as you see the light
six o'clock huh
when i get home i need to do the laundry
then
i wonder what's on tv tonight
i don't have any plans
and it wouldn't be fun playing that game alone
they're in the way
i haven't logged in since that day
i wonder if that snarky afro guy is having a good time nerding out
i'm sorry akito
sorry to stop you
i don't mean to waste your time
i um well
you see
ah must be a high school girl confessing her love
oh to be young again
you sure are one popular guy mister
i remember i also confessed to an upperclassman back when i was in high school
i'm in love with you
i have a girlfriend
that good-looking saito
i wonder how he's doing
um so listen
are we done here
it's been like seven minutes
and you haven't said much since stopping me
can we take this up again some other day
once you've organized your thoughts
sorry but it's almost boss bond time
so i have to go
excuse me then
stop right there
oh of course you've forgotten right
that would make sense
i'm akane
you helped me at that online game event
oh yeah you're the one who got hammered and puked at my place
i'm still very sorry about that incident
uh forget that for a second
Yamada was pretty harsh huh
couldn't you see that girl was making a confession
you should have heard her out
really i was being confessed to
maybe instead of gaming you should learn about the subtleties of human nature
so i've been told
then you're in high school
yamada
i am
right
you were drinking soda the whole time at the izakaya
yeah
what year are you
third
wait that's a toasty academy uniform
that must mean he's pretty smart huh
it's tough to get into that school
huh
actually i was hoping i might run into you again somewhere
sorry i found it later but i stepped on it
the heart
it's broken in half
thanks for going to all the trouble
have you been carrying it the whole time
well i heard that we live near the same station
so i thought i might run into you
i guess i should have logged in
must have been a hassle
it's fine
thanks i was planning to toss it out anyway so don't worry about it
okay i'll be going now
please use this don't worry about returning it
well if you'll excuse me now
please use this
i was planning to toss it out anyway so don't worry about it
coming
hello there it's tagawa express here
you have a delivery for mrs kinoshita
we'll just leave these inside all right
thank you for your business
akone i'm writing to discuss the state of your room here
i'd like to turn it into my training room
so take your belongings okay
thank you
so
what do you need me for
you gotta help me momo
it's so cluttered and i have nowhere to stand
my mom sent all my stuff out of the blue
but look at how much there is
momo what do i do now
oh what a drag
i say toss it all
you can start with that humongous bear
wait i have fond memories of that bear
memories of my grandma
i don't want to hear it
next stop
next
akane
what do you want to do with these things you need them
are they important to you
the umbrella's new so i figured you'll still be using it but since the necklace is broken can i throw it away
then you can start by being more selective
there's only so much storage to be had
be selective
uh
i can't hold on to every single thing
no matter how precious they are to me
so you ended up not tossing that one out after all huh
but i'm throwing out everything else
because i don't need them
not anymore
all right
how about we hit the barbecue place and live it up
your treat of course akane
money's a bit tight so please take it easy on me
yes
hey there yamara i came by to return your umbrella
oh wow this guy really is a dreamboat isn't he
uh you can call me momo
it's very nice to meet you yamara
there you go
what's wrong
something bothering you
no it's
i just don't know what to say
hey yamara
i'm so sorry akane's always troubling you
but hear me out
you should make the most of the opportunity before you so
why not go out with me and maybe we'll get married
you should know i'm very close to calling the cops
i told you not to worry about returning it
do you know how annoying this is
um well
i hear you about the umbrella
i do
but aside from that
i came here to say thank you
i'm glad you were there on the day of that event yamara
truly
had i been alone
it would have been really rough for me
i'm just
are you okay
really thankful
right
okay
we'll head out before you call the cops on us
appreciate it
come on momo
we're going home
walk like a big girl
you can do it
be careful and watch your step here momo
by the way
duty
i mean
the guild master was
worried about you
last i heard they were saying that you haven't logged in since that day
so
well you know
if you're ever free sometime
yeah of course
soon as i get home
i'm gonna log in right away
what about you yamara
i'm going to bed
you're not gonna play
no
you're not
we're getting married
whoo
how to play
no
i'm gonna be
need
you
Howl to go!
Whyl?
Whoa! They're multiplying!
What should we do, Yamada?
Uh, Yamada?
Hey! Yamada?
Hey! What's wrong?
Yamada! Yamada! Yamada! Yamada! Yamada! Yamada! Yamada!
Thank you.